<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CAARMS</string>

    <string name="title_activity_login">Login to CAARMS</string>
    <string name="title_activity_welcome">Welcome to CAARMS</string>
    <string name="title_activity_signup">Signup</string>
    <string name="title_activity_admin">Admin</string>
    <string name="title_activity_survey">Survey</string>


    <!-- Signup -->
    <string name="signup_name">Name</string>
    <string name="signup_email">Email</string>
    <string name="signup_email_hint">Maximum of 40 characters</string>

    <string name="contact_name">Name</string>
    <string name="contact_name_hint">Maximum of 30 characters</string>

    <string name="contact_email">Email</string>
    <string name="contact_email_hint">Maximum of 40 characters</string>

    <string name="contact_nnumber">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="contact_nnumber_hint">Maximum of 20 characters</string>
    
    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="pin">Pin</string>
    <string name="pin_hint">6 digits</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>
    <string name="login">Log In</string>
    <string name="signup">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="incorrect">Incorrect Username/Pin</string>


    <!-- Welcome Screen -->
    <string name="takesurvey">Take Survey</string>
    <string name="nosurveys">No Surveys to Take</string>
    <string name="welcomeTitle">Welcome to CAARMS</string>
    <string name="welcomeMessage">Please log in when notified and click the button
        below to take a survey. At the end of the survey, you will also be able to send a picture, as well
        as respond to suggestions.
        \n \n Useful information: \n Call 0000 000 000 for assistance.\nOffice hours:\n 9am-5pm Mon-Sat\nClosed Sunday.
    </string>
    <string name="welcomeMessage2">Please log in when notified and click the button
        below to take a survey.
        \n Office hours:\n 9am-5pm Mon-Sat\nClosed Sunday.
    </string>


    <!-- Notifications -->
    <string name="notification_ticker_take_survey_title">Please take a survey</string>
    <string name="notification_content_take_survey_title">Login to CAARMS to take a survey</string>
    <string name="notification_content_take_survey_text"> is ready to be taken.</string>


    <!-- Surveys -->
    <string-array name="survey0">
        <item>What was the date that a change was first noted?</item>
        <item>How old were you?</item>
        <item>What were the first symptoms?</item>
        <item>Any history of first-degree relatives with psychosis?</item>
        <item>If yes, please state who</item>
        <item>Please state any medication used, past or present</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="survey1">
            <item>Have you had the feeling that something odd is going on that
        you can’t explain? What is it like?</item>
            <item>Do you feel puzzled by anything? Do familiar surroundings feel
        strange?</item>
            <item>Do you feel that you have changed in some way? How?</item>
            <item>Do you feel that others, or the world, have changed in some
        way?</item>
            <item>Have you felt that
        someone, or something, outside yourself has been controlling
        your thoughts, feelings, actions or urges? Have you had
        feelings or impulses that don’t seem to come from yourself?</item>
            <item>Do you get any strange sensations in your
        body? Do you know what causes them? Could it be due to
        other people or forces outside yourself?</item>
            <item>Have you felt that ideas or thoughts that are
        not your own have been put into your head? How do you know
        they are not your own? Where do they come from?</item>
            <item>Have you ever felt that ideas or thoughts
        are being taken out of your head? How does that happen?</item>
            <item>Are your thoughts broadcast so that
        other people know what you are thinking?</item>
            <item> Can other people read your mind?</item>
            <item> Have you felt that things that were
        happening around you had a special meaning, or that people
        were trying to give you messages? What is it like? How did it
        start?</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="survey2">
            <item> Has anybody been giving you a
        hard time or trying to hurt you? Do you feel like people have
        been talking about you, laughing at you, or watching you? What
        is it like? How do you know this?</item>
            <item> Do you feel you deserve punishment for anything
        you have done wrong?</item>
            <item>Have you had the feeling that something odd is
        going on with your body that you can’t explain? What is it like?
        Do you feel that your body has changed in some way, or that
        there is a problem with your body shape?</item>
            <item>Have you ever felt that you, or a part of you, did
        not exist, or was dead? Do you ever feel that the world does not
        exist?</item>
            <item>Are you very religious? Have you had any
        religious experiences?</item>
            <item> Have you been feeling that you are especially
        important in some way, or that you have powers to do things that
        other people can’t do?</item>
            <item>Is anyone in love with you? Who? How do
        you know this? Do you return his/her feelings?</item>
            <item>Are you a jealous person? Do you worry about
        relationships that your spouse/girlfriend/boyfriend has with other
        people?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="survey3">
        <item>  Is there a change in the way things look to
    you? Do things somehow look different, or abnormal? Are there
    alterations in colour, or brightness of objects (things seeming
    brighter, or duller in colour)? Are there alterations in the size and
    shape of objects? Do things seem to be moving?</item>
        <item>Do you have visions, or see things that may not
    really be there? Do you ever see things that others can’t, or don’t
    seem to? What do you see? At the time that you see these
    things, how real do they seem? Do you realise they are not real
    at the time, or only later?</item>
        <item>Is there any change in the way things
    sound to you? Do things somehow sound different, or
    abnormal? Does your hearing seem more acute, or have
    increased sensitivity? Does your hearing seem muted, or less
    acute?</item>
        <item>Do you ever hear things that may not really be
    there? Do you ever hear things that other people seem not to
    (such as sounds or voices)? What do you hear? At the time you
    hear these things, how real do they seem? Do you realise they
    are not real at the time, or only later?</item>
        <item>Does your sense of smell seem to be
    different, such as more, or less intense, than usual?</item>
        <item>Do you ever smell things that other people don’t
    notice? At the time, do these smells seem real? Do you realise
    they are not real at the time, or only later?</item>
        <item>Does your sense of taste seem to be
    different, such as more, or less intense, than usual?</item>
        <item>Do you ever get any odd tastes in your mouth?
    At the time that you taste these things, how real do they seem?
    Do you realise they are not real at the time, or only later?</item>
        <item>Do you ever get strange
    feelings on, or just beneath, your skin? At the time that you feel
    these things, how real do they seem? Do you realise they are
    not real at the time, or only later?</item>
        <item>Do you ever get strange feelings in your
    body (eg feel that parts of your body have changed in some way,
    or that things are working differently)? Do you feel/think that
    there is a problem with some part, or all of your body, i.e. that it
    looks different to others, or is different in some way? How real
    does this seem?</item>
        <item>Have you noticed any change in your bodily
    sensations, such as increased, or reduced intensity? Or unusual
    bodily sensations such as pulling feelings, aches, burning,
    numbness, vibrations? </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="survey4">
        <item>Do you notice any difficulties with your speech, or ability
    to communicate with others?</item>
        <item>Do you have trouble finding the correct word at the
    appropriate time? </item>
        <item>Do you ever use words that are not quite right, or totally
    irrelevant?</item>
        <item>Have you found yourself going off on tangents when
    speaking and never getting to the point? Is this a recent
    change?</item>
        <item>Are you aware that you are talking about irrelevant
    things, or going off the track?</item>
        <item>Do other people ever seem to have difficulty in
    understanding what you are trying to say/trouble getting
    your message across?</item>
        <item>Do you ever find yourself repeating the words of others?</item>
        <item>Do you ever have to use gesture or mime to
    communicate due to trouble getting your message
    across? How bad is this?</item>
        <item>Does it ever make you want to stay silent and not say
    anything?</item>
        <item>Is it difficult to follow what the subject is saying at times
    due to using incorrect words, being circumstantial or
    tangential?</item>
        <item>Is the subject vague, overly abstract or concrete? Can
    responses be condensed?</item>
        <item>Do they go off the subject often and get lost in their
    words? Do they appear to have difficulty finding the right
    words?</item>
        <item>Do they repeat words that you have used or adopt
    strange words (or ‘non-words’) in the course of regular
    conversation?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="survey5">
        <item>Have you been feeling angry, or irritable recently? Has there been a
    reason for this? Have you felt more irritated than usual at small
    things? Have you been in more arguments with others than usual
    recently? Have you been taking more risks (i.e. when driving)
    recently than usual? Have others commented that your behaviour is
    becoming risky, or unsafe? Have you felt like striking out at people
    or objects recently (more so than usual)?</item>
        <item>Have you become so angry at someone that you have had thoughts
    of hurting them, or destroying their property? Have you acted on
    these thoughts?</item>
        <item>Has the subject been acting in an aggressive or dangerous manner
    recently? Have there been any recent episodes of anger
    outbursts/physical confrontation? Is this how the subject normally
    behaves? Have others commented on a change in their level of
    anger, or irritability? Has the subject destroyed property lately (in
    association with anger)? Have you felt safe with the subject recently
    (i.e. when driving, at otherwise normal times)?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="survey6">
        <item>Have you had any thoughts recently about harming, or killing
    yourself? How often have you felt this way?</item>
        <item>Have you had any thoughts of what you would do to achieve
    this?</item>
        <item>Have you acted on those thoughts at all? What happened?</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="surveys">
        <item>@array/survey0</item>
        <item>@array/survey1</item>
        <item>@array/survey2</item>
        <item>@array/survey3</item>
        <item>@array/survey4</item>
        <item>@array/survey5</item>
        <item>@array/survey6</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="signup_tabs">
        <item>Profile</item>
        <item>Survey</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>
